



EDUCATION

Business Administration

Can Tho University 2012 - 2016

SKILLS

- Language: Vietnamese, English, Chinese
- Communication: Strong
 Presentation, Problem -Solving and Customer Services.
- **Teamwork**: Time Management, Work Under Pressure
- Sales: Product Promotion and Negotiation

AWARDS

- January 2023: Top 5 excellent Performance of The Year (Year end party Flight Operation Unit)
 Organized by Cabin Crew
 Department.
- March 2022: Consolation Prize (Content Creator) - "All roads lead to Bamboo" Contest Organized by Bamboo Airways.
- December 2019 : 2nd Runner Up
- PVcombank's top talent
 Organized by PVcomBank.

VO NGOC BAO TRAN

Cabin Crew

PROFILE

An experienced cabin crew member with four years of aviation service. I enjoy working with people and receiving positive feedback from passengers and co - workers. Furthermore, I demonstrate the ability to solve problems, deal with unusual conditions, and work under pressure.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BAMBOO AIRWAYS - Business Cabin Crew Jan 2021 - Feb 2024

Attended 1800+ hours of domestic and international flight, and was certified in all safety and emergency procedures. First aid and inflight services.

Being in charge of checking safety equipment - Keeping in mind flight safety and security.

Experienced in business class leader who lectures, guides, and transfers knowledge.

Understand how to look after VIP and C-level passengers.

Honorable mention for successfully enforcing the company's SOPs on every flight.

Resolving passenger issues with the highest level of performance. Being a professional in team work with a diverse range of multicultural colleagues.

FREELANCE - Choreographer

2013 - Present

Staging, lecturing, and performing at festivals, conferences, and year - end programs for businesses.

Take part in charity performances to benefit people in need.

PVcomBANK - Relationship Manager Jan 2018 - Mar 2020

Provide savings, loan, and credit card consulting services to consumers. Assist customers with information processing and account management.

Search for new customers to utilize the bank's products.

ALAGON HOTEL & SPA - Receptionist

Jan 2017- Dec 2017

Check-in and check-out for customers.

Provide support, answer inquiries, and handle unforeseen circumstances during guests' stay at the hotel. Recommend restaurants and domestic tours to guests.